<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title> on M.K.C. </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://mkcee.com/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 22:45:39 HKT</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>index</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 22:45:39 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/</guid>
      <description>personal projects some coursework DeDuplicatus - A Deduplication-Enabled Multi-Cloud App web-instagram - Web Instagram written in python CGI youtube-remote - YouTube Remote using socket.io shopping-website - A fast, secure, and user-friendly shopping website prototype non-photorealistic-rendering - CSCI 3290 Computational Photography Project neural-network-project - CSCI3230 Project opengl-playground - CSCI3260 Assignment 2 linux-shell - CENG3150 Programming Assignment 1 chatroom - CENG3150 Programming Assignment 2 java-database-project - CSCI3170 GROUP PROJECT hadoop-wordcount - CSCI4180</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say Hello</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 18:47:10 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vim is the worst text editor ever</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/post/vim-is-the-worst-text-editor-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 15:48:30 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/post/vim-is-the-worst-text-editor-ever/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;except you have built your own config I started my vimrc from bling/dotvim. Then I tried to find more config from some popular &amp;ldquo;Vimers&amp;rdquo;. Here&amp;rsquo;s the list: tpope/tpope Valloric/dotfiles tarruda/dot-files jasonlong/dotfiles ajh17/dotfiles romainl/dotvim jdavis/dotfiles Hope you find it useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 13:18:47 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to WordPress Hugo. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start blogging! This site is using Hugo, which is a static site generator. Unlike systems like WordPress, it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t automatically generate the first post like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 13:18:19 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Mok Ka Chun and I am graduated from The Chinese University of Hong Kong with a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science. Currently this site is sill in alpha stage and there is no brilliant thing to show. But you can browse some of my personal projects or blog posts to know more about me. Contact: mkc188@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

