<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title> on M.K.C. </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://mkcee.com/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 22:45:39 HKT</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>index</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 22:45:39 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/</guid>
      <description>personal projects command-line tools DeDuplicatus - A Deduplication-Enabled Multi-Cloud App web-instagram - Assignment 1 - Web Instagram youtube-remote - Assignment 2 - YouTube Remote shopping-website - a fast, secure, and user-friendly shopping website opengl-playground - CSCI3260 Assignment 2 non-photorealistic-rendering - CSCI 3290 Computational Photography Project neural-network-project - CSCI3230 Project linux-shell - CENG3150 Programming Assignment 1 java-database-project - CSCI3170 GROUP PROJECT hadoop-wordcount - CSCI4180 Assignment 1 fake-ireserve-bot - Fake iReserve Bot (Chrome Extension) csci3290 - CSCI3290 Assignment Collection csci3180 - CSCI3180 Assignment Collection chatroom - CENG3150 Programming Assignment 2 Othello - A command line Othello game written in C++ drift-runners - A real time multiplayer top-down car game vim plugins Code blocks use the solarized theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say Hello</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 18:47:10 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>second</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/post/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 15:48:30 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/post/second/</guid>
      <description>Hello again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 13:18:47 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/post/first/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Pixyll</title>
      <link>http://mkcee.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 13:18:19 HKT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkcee.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This Jekyll theme was crafted with &amp;lt;3 by John Otander (@4lpine). Checkout the Github repository to download it, request a feature, report a bug, or contribute. It&amp;rsquo;s free, and open source (MIT). Thanks to the following: BASSCSS Jekyll Refills Solarized</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

